A sudden 90 degree shift in Earth's magnetic pole plunges the equator into the deepest freeze
possible - absolute zero. Florida has four hours before becoming an arctic tundra.
Absolute Zero is a action, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Robert Lee.
INTER SCI climatologist Dr.
David Kotzman has evidence that a shift in the Earth's polarity
triggered the last Ice Age...in a single day.
Now, it's happening again, and there's no time to escape.
As the temperature plummets, Miami is blasted with snow and ice.
Evacuation routes are jammed.
The only chance David, his old flame Bryn, and a few other hopeful survivors
have is to hole themselves up in a special chamber at INTER SCI.
A desperate race for survival is ignited as nature's fury rages and the
temperature plunges toward -459.67° F...ABSOLUTE ZERO!
Dr. David Kotzman, played by Jeff Fahey.
Bryn, played by Erika Eleniak.
Dr. Veet, played by Bill Dow.
Sophie Miller, played by Jessica Amlee.
A.J. Carmichael, played by Britt Irvin.
Phillip, played by Fred Ewanuick.
Absolute Power is a 1997 American political action thriller film produced by, directed by, and starring Clint Eastwood
as a master jewel thief, Luther Whitney, who witnesses the killing of a woman by Secret Service agents.
The screenplay by William Goldman is based on the 1996
novel Absolute Power by David Baldacci.
Screened at the 1997 Cannes Film Festival, the film also stars Gene Hackman, Ed Harris,
Laura Linney, Judy Davis, Scott Glenn, Dennis Haysbert, and Richard Jenkins.
It was also the last screen appearance of E.
The scenes in the museum were filmed in the Walters Art Museum, where Whitney is
copying a painting by El Greco: "Saint Francis Receiving the Stigmata".
The film explores themes of florida, beautiful woman, climatologist.
The tone is uplifting and thought_provoking.